<?xml version="1.0"?>
<products>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>127474189951499578</id>
		<name>Rogue Starter Acoustic Guitar</name>
		<description>
			The small-bodied Rogue Starter Acoustic Guitar is an amazing deal for a starter guitar. Its smaller profile (7/8" scale) makes it very playable for kids or aspiring guitarists with smaller body frames and hands. It has a maple neck and rosewood fretboard and Martin strings which help.give you a nice tone.

			Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>2488</price>
		<filename>a1.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>127474169147029886</id>
		<name>Rogue RA-090 Dreadnought Acoustic Guitar</name>
		<description>
			From Rogue comes this amazing deal in the RA-90 dreadnought acoustic guitar. The Rogue guitar is an ideal instrument for the beginner, or young musician. The body depth and width bring out balanced tone and plenty of projection to be heard from across the room.

			This ultra-affordable dreadnought acoustic guitar features a whitewood body, which brings out lots of mid-range punch. The nato neck adds sustain without losing any strength in tone. The painted maple bridge and fingerboard add clarity to each note, and a striking look to the front of the guitar. The RA-090's C-shape neck, 1-2/3" nut width, and 16" radius help with intricate fretboard movements when running up and down the 20 frets. The RA-90 also features nickel hardware and covered tuners. This Rogue acoustic guitar will certainly get the job done, at a price that anybody can afford.

			Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>3245</price>
		<filename>a2.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1275776901305</id>
		<name>Rogue RG-624 Left-Handed Dreadnought Acoustic Guitar Natural</name>
		<description>
			The RG-624 Left-Handed Guitar features a spruce top for a great sound, die-cast tuning machines for precise tuning, inlaid body binding, and world famous Martin strings.

			Case sold separately
		</description>
		<price>4868</price>
		<filename>a3.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1416527659428826548</id>
		<name>Rogue RA-090 Concert Cutaway Acoustic-Electric Guitar</name>
		<description>
			The super-affordable Rogue RA-090 Concert Acoustic-Electric Guitar is an excellent entry-level 25.4 in. scale guitar with laminate whitewood body and top finished off by a natural gloss to keep it in peak condition for years. Other features include a single cutaway, nato C-shaped neck, simulated rosewood fingerboard, simulated rosewood belly bridge, and an ivory color plastic saddle and nut. Rounding out its fabulous features is an Eden MET-A06 undersaddle pickup system with 3-band EQ and tuner.
		</description>
		<price>4868</price>
		<filename>a4.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1415030763497</id>
		<name>Mitchell MX420 Grand Auditorium Acoustic-Electric Guitar Midnight Black Finish</name>
		<description>
			Expanding on their successful MX400 Series of acoustic-electric guitars, the MX420 offers superior playability and comfort, along with amazing good looks in an affordable stage-ready instrument.

			This grand auditorium shallow body features a top, back, and sides made from exquisite, highly-figured quilted ash burl in a custom Midnight Black finish, complimented by a custom abalone rosette.

			It also features Mitchell's CE304T preamp with a built-in tuner and 3-band EQ. Like all Mitchells, the MX420 gets a complete professional setup in the USA to make sure each one plays perfect.
		</description>
		<price>24343</price>
		<filename>a5.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1321990087183</id>
		<name>Mitchell MX400 Exotic Wood Acoustic-Electric Guitar Quilted Ash Burl</name>
		<description>
			The Mitchell MX400 Exotics Series Acoustic-Electric Guitar is a member of the Exotics series of exotic wood acoustic-electric guitars. This grand auditorium shallow body guitar features the CE304T preamp with built-in tuner.

			The shifted, scalloped X-bracing is a feature typically found on guitars costing several times more, and helps ensure incredible sound. The MX400 gets a complete professional setup in the USA to make sure it plays perfectly. Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>21638</price>
		<filename>a6.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1500000029397</id>
		<name>Rogue RA-090 Dreadnought 12-String Acoustic Guitar Regular Natural</name>
		<description>
				Rogue proudly introduces the 12-string version of one of their most popular guitars. The Rogue RA090-12 guitar is an ideal instrument to introduce beginners and young musicians to the chimey overtones of the 12-string. The body depth and width bring out balanced tone and plenty of projection to be heard from across the room.
		</description>
		<price>8114</price>
		<filename>a7.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1500000042918</id>
		<name>Mitchell O120CESB Acoustic Electric Guitar 3-Color Sunburst</name>
		<description>
				The orchestra-sized Mitchell O120CESB cutaway acoustic-electric guitar is perfect for musicians looking to expand their arsenal or for those who find larger guitars less comfortable. It features a select spruce top and mahogany back and sides for great tone and remarkably loud volume. Multi-ply body binding, abalone sound hole rosette, and a high-gloss vintage sunburst finish add to its stunning good looks, giving it the classic vibe of a timeless instrument. It also features a beautifully bound fingerboard and sealed, die-cast tuners for easy and stable tuning. Plus, built-in top-grade electronics with 3-band EQ and tuner let you tailor your sound then amplify it through any instrument amplifier or PA system.
		</description>
		<price>8114</price>
		<filename>a8.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1396278325285</id>
		<name>Alvarez DYMR70 Yairi Masterworks Dreadnought Acoustic Guitar Sunburst</name>
		<description>
				The Alvarez DYMR70 Yairi Masterworks Dreadnought Acoustic Guitar is crafted by a master luthier to meet the needs of the most demanding guitarist. The finest woods were selected and no corners cut to make this outstanding steel string guitar. You could spend more, but you won't find a better example of guitar builder's personal pursuit of perfection. This Yairi is truly somthing special. Includes a nice hardshell case.

				Yairi
				The wonderful thing about making acoustic guitars is that they are incredibly sensitive and complex instruments. Decades, careers, lifetimes have been spent trying to perfect or find the sound in the luthier's head, but often it eludes us. Only time, experimentation and experience can help guitar companies get the results guitarists are after.

				Alvarez-Yairi guitars have held a special place in players' hearts for nearly fifty years. Some of the greatest songwriters and guitarists ever to grace the planet have played them. So when it comes to updating the Alvarez-Yairi Series, Alvarez did it with great care and the reverence it deserves.

				Two years of development have resulted in producing the finest guitars Alvarez have ever made. Eloquently voiced instruments, beautifully balanced with a charisma and tonal personality you will fall in love with.

				The all-new Alvarez-Yairi Series is simply superb.
		</description>
		<price>108140</price>
		<filename>a9.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1321397765887</id>
		<name>Rainsong Shorty Acoustic-Electric Guitar High Gloss finish</name>
		<description>
				The SG Shorty Acoustic-Electric is RainSong's smallest and most refined body shape with a unidirectional soundboard, hybrid body construction, and a short scale 12-fret neck -- the perfect combination for an intimate instrument with a warm tone and surprising punch.

				Shorty's neck joins the body at the 12th fret rather than the 14th fret. This moves the bridge back on the soundboard towards the center of the lower bout resulting in improved sonic energy transmission from the strings to the soundboard and enhanced bass response.

				Unidirectional carbon mimics the tight grain of a fine Spruce soundboard. First introduced on the Concert Series, this soundboard is RainSong's lightest. The Hybrid body technology blends the crystalline highs of carbon with the mellow tones of glass. The synergy between the unidirectional soundboard and the hybrid body is obvious from Shorty's first strum.

				The SG features a high-gloss, UV protective, polyurethane finish that magnifies the 3 dimensional carbon weaves on the instrument. Includes case.
		</description>
		<price>108140</price>
		<filename>a10.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1396278325333</id>
		<name>Alvarez WY1TS Yairi Stage OM/Folk Acoustic-Electric Guitar Natural</name>
		<description>
				A wonderful performance guitar or just for playing for pleasure, the Alvarez Yairi WY1, from the Bob Weir Series AC/EL Folk line, is a medium-depth acoustic guitar with a single cutaway and select tonewoods, most notably a select AA Western red cedar top. The grain on these tops is very close and even, and in concert with the rosewood back and sides, the overall appearance of this instrument is striking. Gloss finish with tobacco sunburst.

				The top is bound in ivoroid and features a double circle rosette around the centered sound hole. The neck is made of mahogany and is attached to the body with a dovetail joint set at the 14th fret. As soon as you lift this guitar out of the wood frame case it comes with, its quality is evident. The detail, the balance and the stunning beauty of the woods instills a great sense of appreciation for the workmanship and design. It features side dots for player orientation, and a lovely custom inlay at the 12th fret. It is comfortable to wear and sounds great acoustically.

				The onboard L.R. Baggs Stagepro Element is a side-mounted preamp/EQ that offers battery access and a full chromatic tuner that is hidden beneath the control panel to maintain a clean, classy look. The three-band EQ with phase inversion and Garrett Null notch filter controls deliver warm, pristine sound even under the most challenging conditions. The system includes the Element pickup and pre-wired strapjack.
		</description>
		<price>108140</price>
		<filename>a11.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Acoustic</category>
		<id>1274228073593</id>
		<name>Rainsong Hybrid Series H-OM1000N2 Slim Body Cutaway Acoustic-Electric Guitar</name>
		<description>
				The RainSong Hybrid Series combines carbon fiber with glass fiber construction to achieve the signature RainSong sound and road-tough stability at an attractive price. This Orchestra Model is the smallest and most refined of all RainSong's shapes. The glass and carbon fiber guitar is also the company's most comfortable and intimate guitar, with an immediacy of presence that makes it a favorite with the coffee house crowd. The treble, already a breathtaking attribute of RainSong, and the carbon sound are simply sublime in this little guitar. Crystal clarity, balance, superb separation of individual notes, and an expansive dynamic range make the RainSong H-OM1000N2 an individually expressive acoustic-electric guitar.

				Because of Projection Tuned Layering, the H-OM1000N2 acoustic-electric guitar is capable of strong projection. It won't rattle windows like the Jumbo or the Dreadnought, but the RainSong OM, when driven, packs a lot of power and punch for a small-bodied glass and carbon fiber guitar. The neck is a result of an extensive, long-term collaboration with the renowned artist Steve Miller and Master Luthier John Bolin.

				The neck design is based on a modified "U" profile that has been popular in guitars since the 1950s. It has a substantial feel that is ergonomically sound and results in better transfer of string vibration energy to the soundboard. This acoustic-electric guitar features a truss rod that is accessible from the headstock. Graphite does not warp or bow with changes in humidity and temperature, so the purpose of a truss rod is to allow customization of the relief to suit individual preferences.

				At the heart of the RainSong guitar is an impressive electronics system, the Fishman Prefix+T. This preamp features ultraquiet electronics and volume, Bass, treble, and semi-parametric contour controls. In addition to a built-in chromatic tuner, the Prefix+T adds a brilliance control and a phase switch and notch filter to help fight feedback.
		</description>
		<price>102730</price>
		<filename>a12.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1500000018787</id>
		<name>G&amp;L Limited Edition Tribute ASAT Classic Bluesboy Electric Guitar Turquoise Mist</name>
		<description>
				The G&amp;L ASAT Classic Bluesboy is a factory-modded version of the traditional single-cutaway bolt-on axe. For players looking for the unmistakable warmth of a classic humbucker in the neck position, the Bluesboy delivers with a well-balanced pairing of a G&amp;L alnico humbucker and a single-coil G&amp;L bridge pickup.

				Framed in a classic boxed-steel bridge, the single-coil alnico bridge pickup delivers crisp attack with complex harmonics while individual brass saddles offer modern levels of intonation refinement. Flip to the neck ‘bucker and you’ll discover all the charismatic warmth you could ask for. Put them together and you’ll enjoy a whole new level of pleasure.

				The Tribute Series ASAT Classic Bluesboy is dripping with mojo at a price attainable for every working musician. This model comes in a special limited-edition finish with a 3-ply white pickguard and maple fretboard. Once you play a G&amp;L Tribute Series, you’ll never look back. Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>24343</price>
		<filename>e1.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1288121575633</id>
		<name>Rogue RR100 Rocketeer Electric Guitar</name>
		<description>
				The Rocketeer RR100 electric guitar is Rogue's take on a classic design, built for ease of playability. It is constructed with a lightweight contoured double-cutaway paulownia body. The ultra-thin, comfortable maple neck makes it easy to fly up and down the 22-fret fingerboard with ease.

				The humbucker/dual single-coil pickup configuration with a 5-way switch allows for a wide-variety of tones. A 6-screw vintage tremolo lets you have tons of whammy bar fun, while the Rogue Rocketeer's die-cast tuners ensure solid tuning stability. Guitar case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>5409</price>
		<filename>e2.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1500000000009770</id>
		<name>Mitchell MM100 Mini Double Cutaway Electric Guitar</name>
		<description>
				The Mitchell MM100 features a short-scale double cutaway basswood body and a one-piece maple neck with smooth fretboard. It comes complete with two high-output ceramic humbucker pickups that crank out enough juice for a guitar twice its size. High-ratio tuners allow for precise tuning control, while the traditional, adjustable TOM-style bridge provides solid intonation. Plus, the MM100’s string-through body design gives it plenty of sustain and bite. 

				All Mitchell electric guitars receive a complete stateside setup and quality control inspection to ensure exceptional playability. Available in Walnut Satin (WS), Black (BK) and Blood Red (BR). Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>5409</price>
		<filename>e3.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1500000000009761</id>
		<name>Mitchell MD300 Modern Rock Double Cutaway Electric Guitar</name>
		<description>
				The Mitchell MD300 features a carved top, double cutaway, basswood body and a one-piece, bolt-on maple neck, offering outstanding resonance and articulation. For a more advanced, modern sound, there's a rail-style ceramic humbucker in the bridge and a mini-rail Alnico V humbucker in the neck position. They both provide a more consistent magnetic pull versus standard pole pieces, which enhances overall tone and sustain. It also allows for additional picking room for advanced players while also expanding the visual beauty of the guitar top. The string-thru body design increases sustain even further, and high-ratio locking tuning machines make precise tuning easy.

				Before delivery to our dealers, all Mitchell electric guitars receive a complete stateside setup and quality control inspection to ensure exceptional playability. Available in Walnut Satin (WS), Black (BK) and Blood Red (BR). Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>16228</price>
		<filename>e4.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1500000025458</id>
		<name>Friedman Vintage-T P90s Mahogany Body Rosewood Fingerboard Electric Guitar Gold Parchment Pickguard</name>
		<description>
				The love of vintage guitars is a passion which drives many guitarists to seek out those classic instruments of yesteryear. This same passion brought together two seasoned veterans in the guitar world, Dave Friedman &amp; Grover Jackson, to bring you a new classic.

				The Friedman USA Custom Shop is proud to present the Vintage-T collection, using only the finest masterfully aged hardwoods, genuine nitro finish, Plek'd-finished fretwork and Friedman custom-wound pickups. A lifelong passion and legendary craftsmanship is the heart and soul of the Friedman Vintage-T collection.

				In the last few years Friedman has taken the tube amp market by storm on a worldwide basis. The instant players plug into a Friedman amp there is something familiar - but there’s more - that special something that makes them want to keep playing and playing - and then own one, regardless of cost.

				In reality, a Friedman amp is just a set parts - capacitors, resistors, wire, transformers, potentiometers and switches etc... Individually, none of these components deliver the “Secret Sauce” that makes a Friedman a Friedman. The secret sauce is, in fact, simply a series of choices made by Dave Friedman, using his trained ears, 20-plus years of experience working on amplifiers and the highest level of craftsmanship. Which parts? What value? Used where? Connected how? In which configuration? These answers, and Dave’s painstaking attention to every nuance is what delivers the tone players seek. This neurosis is the reason Dave himself bench tests, plays-in and then signs EVERY amp before it leaves the shop.

				It is this same relentless perseverance that makes Friedman guitars so special. Many people know Dave’s history of working on amplifiers and building rigs for rock’s elite players. What most people don’t know is that Dave’s passion and knowledge of guitars is just as deep. Dave has been consulting for and advising guitar companies in the background for years.

				This wealth of knowledge is infused into the new Vintage-T Collection. Just like every Friedman amps, in their raw state, Friedman guitars are just wood, frets, tuners and pickups etc... The “Secret Sauce” is all of the subtle choices Dave made, then brought to life by legendary guitar builder, Grover Jackson.

				Plug into a Vintage T and you will be inspired to play and keep playing. A carefully seasoned mixture of the familiar and that which is new.

				Premium body woods - Dave chose genuine Mahogany and Alder as the body woods of choice for their classic tonal character. Each piece of wood is hand-selected by Grover Jackson himself. In the last round of building 25 guitars, over 500 wood planks were inspected by Grover - 475 did not make the cut. Grain pattern and light weight are benchmarks for every Vintage-T guitar.

				Necks -Select eastern hard maple with your choice of Indian Rosewood or maple fingerboard is available.

				Frets – Jescar FW47095 nickel silver fret wire is used on Vintage-T guitars.

				Compound Radius - Grover Jackson invented the compound radius fingerboard (CRF) 35 years ago. The fingerboard geometry is based on a conical shape rather than cylindrical. The significance is tangible and substantial – a 10”-14” compound radius fingerboard allows for maximum playability with no chance of your strings fretting out when bending. Compound radius is time-consuming and laborious to get exactly right, yet worth-it – and featured on every Friedman Vintage-T.

				Tight Pocket and Exclusive Zero-Shift Neck Pins - Neck shifting results in incorrect string alignment and is a challenge for many guitars. A tight neck pocket helps, but in-and-of itself does not eliminate the problem. Vintage-T guitars raise the bar with the exclusive Zero-Shift Neck Pin design; whereby, two military grade precision steel dowel pins align the body and neck, eliminating shift all together. The tonal benefit of this connection is a virtual fusion of the body and neck whereby the transference of vibration is maximized.

				Tuners – Vintage-style Kluson tuners.

				Plek – Very few boutique builders and many of the giants do not use a PLEK. This West German-made device provides the ultimate in fretboard analysis, fret-leveling and overall setup, and ensures maximum playability of all Friedman guitars.

				Aged Nitrocellulose Finish - Grover Jackson is one of the few guitar manufacturers in Southern California permitted to spray nitrocellulose lacquer. Friedman guitars wear a thin nitro finish allowing the wood to breathe.

				Custom Friedman Pickups – Dave and Grover worked for over a year on the Friedman Classic Humbucker and Classic 90 pickups to get the exact tone Dave envisioned. Both choices feature nickel silver base plates, high quality copper wire and alnico magnets.

				• The Classic 90 delivers a smooth, warm tone with a very open top-end and touch-sensitive dynamics. The combination of slightly over-wound 42 awg wire coils and traditional Alnico V magnets give the Classic 90 a fat, yet extremely articulate tone with excellent response to pick attack.

				• The Friedman Classic Humbucker produces vintage-style tone with an exceptionally balanced frequency response, outstanding clarity and extended dynamic range. These 42 awg pickups are reminiscent of late ‘59 PAFs in tone with a bit more Dave-infused attitude.

				Case included – All Friedman guitars come in a custom G&amp;G case.

				Certificate of Authenticity - Dave Friedman and Grover Jackson carefully inspect each guitar prior to shipping. A serial numbered Certificate of Authenticity signed by both Dave and Grover is included.
		</description>
		<price>146061</price>
		<filename>e5.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1500000025453</id>
		<name>Friedman Vintage-T P90s Rosewood Fingerboard Electric Guitar Metallic Blue Tortoise Pickguard</name>
		<description>
				The love of vintage guitars is a passion which drives many guitarists to seek out those classic instruments of yesteryear. This same passion brought together two seasoned veterans in the guitar world, Dave Friedman &amp; Grover Jackson, to bring you a new classic.

				The Friedman USA Custom Shop is proud to present the Vintage-T collection, using only the finest masterfully aged hardwoods, genuine nitro finish, Plek'd-finished fretwork and Friedman custom-wound pickups. A lifelong passion and legendary craftsmanship is the heart and soul of the Friedman Vintage-T collection.

				In the last few years Friedman has taken the tube amp market by storm on a worldwide basis. The instant players plug into a Friedman amp there is something familiar - but there’s more - that special something that makes them want to keep playing and playing - and then own one, regardless of cost.

				In reality, a Friedman amp is just a set parts - capacitors, resistors, wire, transformers, potentiometers and switches etc... Individually, none of these components deliver the “Secret Sauce” that makes a Friedman a Friedman. The secret sauce is, in fact, simply a series of choices made by Dave Friedman, using his trained ears, 20-plus years of experience working on amplifiers and the highest level of craftsmanship. Which parts? What value? Used where? Connected how? In which configuration? These answers, and Dave’s painstaking attention to every nuance is what delivers the tone players seek. This neurosis is the reason Dave himself bench tests, plays-in and then signs EVERY amp before it leaves the shop.

				It is this same relentless perseverance that makes Friedman guitars so special. Many people know Dave’s history of working on amplifiers and building rigs for rock’s elite players. What most people don’t know is that Dave’s passion and knowledge of guitars is just as deep. Dave has been consulting for and advising guitar companies in the background for years.

				This wealth of knowledge is infused into the new Vintage-T Collection. Just like every Friedman amps, in their raw state, Friedman guitars are just wood, frets, tuners and pickups etc... The “Secret Sauce” is all of the subtle choices Dave made, then brought to life by legendary guitar builder, Grover Jackson.

				Plug into a Vintage T and you will be inspired to play and keep playing. A carefully seasoned mixture of the familiar and that which is new.

				Premium body woods - Dave chose genuine Mahogany and Alder as the body woods of choice for their classic tonal character. Each piece of wood is hand-selected by Grover Jackson himself. In the last round of building 25 guitars, over 500 wood planks were inspected by Grover - 475 did not make the cut. Grain pattern and light weight are benchmarks for every Vintage-T guitar.

				Necks -Select eastern hard maple with your choice of Indian Rosewood or maple fingerboard is available.

				Frets – Jescar FW47095 nickel silver fret wire is used on Vintage-T guitars.

				Compound Radius - Grover Jackson invented the compound radius fingerboard (CRF) 35 years ago. The fingerboard geometry is based on a conical shape rather than cylindrical. The significance is tangible and substantial – a 10”-14” compound radius fingerboard allows for maximum playability with no chance of your strings fretting out when bending. Compound radius is time-consuming and laborious to get exactly right, yet worth-it – and featured on every Friedman Vintage-T.

				Tight Pocket and Exclusive Zero-Shift Neck Pins - Neck shifting results in incorrect string alignment and is a challenge for many guitars. A tight neck pocket helps, but in-and-of itself does not eliminate the problem. Vintage-T guitars raise the bar with the exclusive Zero-Shift Neck Pin design; whereby, two military grade precision steel dowel pins align the body and neck, eliminating shift all together. The tonal benefit of this connection is a virtual fusion of the body and neck whereby the transference of vibration is maximized.

				Tuners – Vintage-style Kluson tuners.

				Plek – Very few boutique builders and many of the giants do not use a PLEK. This West German-made device provides the ultimate in fretboard analysis, fret-leveling and overall setup, and ensures maximum playability of all Friedman guitars.

				Aged Nitrocellulose Finish - Grover Jackson is one of the few guitar manufacturers in Southern California permitted to spray nitrocellulose lacquer. Friedman guitars wear a thin nitro finish allowing the wood to breathe.

				Custom Friedman Pickups – Dave and Grover worked for over a year on the Friedman Classic Humbucker and Classic 90 pickups to get the exact tone Dave envisioned. Both choices feature nickel silver base plates, high quality copper wire and alnico magnets.
				• The Classic 90 delivers a smooth, warm tone with a very open top-end and touch-sensitive dynamics. The combination of slightly over-wound 42 awg wire coils and traditional Alnico V magnets give the Classic 90 a fat, yet extremely articulate tone with excellent response to pick attack.
				• The Friedman Classic Humbucker produces vintage-style tone with an exceptionally balanced frequency response, outstanding clarity and extended dynamic range. These 42 awg pickups are reminiscent of late ‘59 PAFs in tone with a bit more Dave-infused attitude.

				Case included – All Friedman guitars come in a custom G&amp;G case.

				Certificate of Authenticity - Dave Friedman and Grover Jackson carefully inspect each guitar prior to shipping. A serial numbered Certificate of Authenticity signed by both Dave and Grover is included. 
		</description>
		<price>146061</price>
		<filename>e6.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1373474470352</id>
		<name>G&amp;L Comanche Electric Guitar Clear Blue</name>
		<description>
				The G&amp;L Comanche is Leo's final word on the traditional double-cutaway bolt-on axe. Fact is, the first thing you'll notice about the Comanche is the distinctive shape of the Magnetic Field Design Z-Coil pickups designed by Leo Fender himself. These pickups deliver a bright and sparkly top end while offering a robust bottom end, all without any 60-cycle hum.

				You'll find plenty of power in the Z-coil pickups, but what's surprising is how glassy and detailed they become as you roll back the volume and bass controls, the latter a part of the Comanche's PTB (Passive Treble and Bass) system. What's more, the Comanche includes a mini-toggle expander switch to allow neck+bridge or all three pickups together. In a pinch, the neck+bridge combo does a convincing faux ASAT Special.

				Making the most of this delicious combo is Leo's Dual-Fulcrum vibrato, a work of engineering art which allows bending up or down with unsurpassed stability, while offering a silky feel through its beefy aluminum vibrato arm.
		</description>
		<price>114415</price>
		<filename>e7.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1273888005138</id>
		<name>G&amp;L ASAT Classic BluesBoy Electric Guitar Clear Orange</name>
		<description>
				A finely crafted solidbody that plays buttery smooth with gorgeous woods and premium hardware. The Classic Bluesboy has a solid Swamp Ash body with natural wood binding. The hard rock maple neck with ebony fretboard has a beautifully tinted glossy neck finish. The G&amp;L MFD bridge pickup dispenses traditional single-coil bite and the Duncan SH55N Seth Lover churns out vintage ""Patent-Applied-For"" humbucker tones. Schaller tuners. Deluxe appointments and craftsmanship throughout. Includes deluxe hardshell case.

				The patented Magnetic Field Design pickups use a ceramic bar magnet installed underneath each coil, with soft iron adjustable pole pieces to transfer the magnetic field to the surface of the pickup. By contrast, traditional Alnico type pickups, such as used in the Legacy and George Fullerton models, use nonadjustable Alnico pole pieces leaving the only adjustment being pickup height. The Magnetic Field Design has this adjustment, but further offers individual adjustment of each pole piece, letting the player effectively adjust the output of each string on each pickup. Magnetic Field Design (MFD) yield about twice the output per wind, making the pickup quieter while allowing a greater overall output. The sound of Magnetic Field pickups is slightly warmer with a broader frequency response.

				One major Nashville session guitarist remarked that G&amp;L Magnetic Field single-coil pickups sounded as balanced and sweet as his favorite old vintage Alnico equipped axe. The difference is that the MFD pickups sound that good right into his amp without all the EQ tweaking of his mixing console that made his other guitar sound so good. When he ran his G&amp;L though his studio rig, he was truly amazed at the rich and warm, yet clear and sparkly sound.
		</description>
		<price>113603</price>
		<filename>e8.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1373474470637</id>
		<name>G&amp;L Superhawk Jerry Cantrell Signature Model Electric Guitar Ivory</name>
		<description>
				Twenty-something years ago, Jerry Cantrell bought his first G&amp;L Rampage while working at a Dallas music store, and he still rocks 'em hard today. But what Jerry didn't discover at the time was the G&amp;L Superhawk, a hard-charging model like the Rampage equipped with twin 'buckers. That's changed and so will rock history.

				It's been well over two decades since a G&amp;L Superhawk was last produced. Now G&amp;L is proud to announce the launch of the Superhawk Jerry Cantrell Signature Model, available in two USA-made versions as well as a surprisingly affordable G&amp;L Tribute Series version.

				This Superhawk starts out with the same soft maple body and fast-playing hard rock maple neck with ebony fingerboard as the Rampage. It even shares the same Seymour Duncan JB pickup in the bridge position, but adds a Seymour Duncan '59 in the neck position as well as a 3-position pickup selector and tone control with push/pull coil split. The Rampage's Kahler bridge is swapped for a G&amp;L Saddle Lock bridge for improved comfort, stronger sustain and rock-solid tuning stability. This axe is all about capturing the Jerry Cantrell feel while offering more tonal versatility.
		</description>
		<price>97374</price>
		<filename>e9.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1273888005102</id>
		<name>G&amp;L S-500 Deluxe Electric Guitar Cherry Burst</name>
		<description>
				The S500 Deluxe's mahogany body with flame maple top, hard rock maple neck and rosewood fretboard are shaped and finished by hand by expert craftsmen. Each is then fitted with the refined hardware that makes every G&amp;L play like a dream: jumbo frets, Magnetic Field Design G&amp;L single-coil pickups, G&amp;L dual-fulcrum tremolo bridge, and Schaller locking tuners. Special S-500 electronics include 3-band EQ and volume with a push/pull pot for pickup expansion.

				Includes hardshell case.The patented Magnetic Field Design pickups use a ceramic bar magnet installed underneath each coil, with soft iron adjustable pole pieces to transfer the magnetic field to the surface of the pickup. By contrast, traditional Alnico type pickups, such as used in the Legacy and George Fullerton models, use nonadjustable Alnico pole pieces leaving the only adjustment being pickup height. The Magnetic Field Design has this adjustment, but further offers individual adjustment of each pole piece, letting the player effectively adjust the output of each string on each pickup. Magnetic Field Design yield about twice the output per wind, making the pickup quieter while allowing a greater overall output. The sound of Magnetic Field pickups is slightly warmer with a broader frequency response.

				One major Nashville session guitarist remarked that the G&amp;L S-500 with Magnetic Field single coil pickups sounded as balanced and ""sweet"" as his favorite old vintage Alnico equipped axe. The difference is that the S-500 sounds that good right into his amp without all the EQ tweaking of his mixing console that made his other guitar sound so good. When he ran his S-500 though his studio rig, he was truly amazed at the rich and warm, yet clear and sparkly sound.
		</description>
		<price>96157</price>
		<filename>e10.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1500000007308</id>
		<name>Dean Dave Mustaine Signature VMNT Holy Grail</name>
		<description>
				The Dean Guitars USA Dave Mustaine Signature VMNT Holy Grail is constructed from the finest of materials. The 25.5-in. scaled beauty has an all solid mahogany top and body, set mahogany neck, ebony fingerboard, and Mustaine Slim-D neck profile with a 16 in. neck radius. A 1-11/16 in. Graph Tech TUSQ nut, TonePros bridge and 24 medium frets allow full access to the upper register.

				Strung with Dave's signature set of Cleartone Strings and loaded with Dave Mustaine Signature Seymour Duncan Live Wire active pickups, this immaculate show piece plays as good as it appears and is a must have for the discerning guitarist lucky enough to own one. Will include special hard shell case, certificate of authenticity, and engraved Chalice commemorating the guitar's unique features.
		</description>
		<price>378407</price>
		<filename>e11.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Electric</category>
		<id>1500000041494</id>
		<name>Hamer Standard Flame Top Electric Guitar Cherry Sunburst</name>
		<description>
				The Standard is a visually stunning guitar that delivers spectacular sound. This Hamer design is the second body shape ever made by Hamer in 1974 and in essence similar to Hamer USA Standard - an upscale flame top guitar, discontinued in ‘85, revived in ‘95 and incorporated into Import Series in 1997. Updated with a solid maple cap and figured maple veneer on a mahogany body, this guitar screams while also providing good treble clarity. An iconic Hamer design, the STD-CS is tastefully treated with a Cherry Sunburst, gorgeous flame maple top with crown inlays. Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>43277</price>
		<filename>e12.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1274423038555</id>
		<name>Rogue VB100 Violin Bass Guitar Vintage Sunburst</name>
		<description>
				The Rogue VB-100 violin bass guitar features a flamed maple arched top and back with the European-style hollowbody that makes it lightweight and capable of deep, resonant bass tones. The violin bass's traditional 31" scale offers immediate familiarity in your hands. A custom trapeze tailpiece, pearloid pickguard, and body binding on front and back are added touches. Don't be fooled by the tiny price; this Rogue a serious violin bass nicely made with all the playability and tone of the original at a fraction of the cost. 

				Case sold separately.
		</description>
		<price>12442</price>
		<filename>b1.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1389832990308</id>
		<name>Hofner Ignition Series Vintage Violin Bass Sunburst</name>
		<description>
				With authentic details inspired by the original, the Hofner Ignition Series Vintage Bass makes the legendary violin bass available to the rest of us. Don't get the idea that this a just a "nowhere man" look-alike. This quality instrument features a real spruce top and beautiful flamed maple back and sides. The semi-hollow body and set neck will give you the warm, round tone you expect from the violin bass.
		</description>
		<price>18933</price>
		<filename>b2.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1346078188493</id>
		<name>Hofner Shorty Electric Bass Black</name>
		<description>
				The Shorty bass offers the same classic warm Hofner bass tone with a single Hofner humbucker bridge pickup. It offers full-scale length combined with such small overall dimensions that it can be taken anywhere. Other features include a basswood body with a bolt-on maple neck, a rosewood fingerboard with dot inlays, and a fixed metal tailpiece/bridge. Available in black.
		</description>
		<price>10819</price>
		<filename>b3.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1500000031702</id>
		<name>B.C. Rich MK3B Mockingbird Quilted Maple Electric Bass Guitar Gloss Natural</name>
		<description>
				The B.C. Rich Mockingbird MK3B four-string bass offers great tone and playability—and plenty of eye-catching stage presence. With a pair of active split-coil pickups and a proprietary 9-volt preamp, you'll never be short on punishing low-end punch feeding into your amp. And the control layout provides a master volume, blend volume and high- and low-end adjustments for ultimate tone control.

				And the solid mahogany body matched with a hard maple neck that's capped with a 24-fret rosewood fingerboard gives you fantastic tonal projection, a solid feel and classic good looks—despite its obvious wild side. Get your hands on one today.
		</description>
		<price>21638</price>
		<filename>b4.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>127474187174989868</id>
		<name>Palatino VE-550 Electric Upright Bass</name>
		<description>
				The Palatino VE-550 Electric Upright Bass is the answer to many a bass player's prayers. With sweet sound, great looks, and light, portable design, the VE-550 bass has a chambered body of select spruce. The slim, maple neck and curved ebony fingerboard emulate an acoustic upright bass. The Palatino VE-550 bass's adjustable maple bridge rests on the piezo transducer pickup, giving the VE-550 electric upright its large, booming tone.

				Geared tuners with metal buttons offer easy, accurate tuning. The Palatino VE-550 bass's black-finished metal tailpiece is sturdy and practical. The lightweight endpin offers an infinite range of adjustment with a positive locking mechanism.

				The Palatino VE-550 is an extremely versatile electric bass with active tone and volume controls and a headphone jack with preamp. Palatino includes a rugged combination leather/plastic carrying bag with backpack straps.

				The low, effortless action appeals especially to fretted electric bass players making the transition to an upright bass. The Palatino VE-550 Elecric Upright Bass has big tone, much like an amplified acoustic bass. It's an electric upright bass that's sure to please professionals looking for a bass they can travel with.
		</description>
		<price>45441</price>
		<filename>b5.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>127474189240597226</id>
		<name>Lakland Skyline Deluxe 55-02 5-String Bass</name>
		<description>
				A Bartolini humbucker (bridge) and a single-coil (neck) are teamed with the same 3-band active preamp used in the US-made 55-94 to let you dial in an incredible range of tones. 3-way toggle for coil splitting increases tonal range. It has that deep Lakland cutaway on the high register side of the neck that allows easy access to highest frets for throwing licks on top of your grooves. Ash body with a quilt veneer top and deluxe transparent finish.
		</description>
		<price>81091</price>
		<filename>b6.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1500000047711</id>
		<name>Lakland Skyline 44-51 Maple Fretboard 4-String Electric Bass Guitar Blonde</name>
		<description>
				The Lakland Skyline 44-51 shares the same slab body aesthetics of the US 44-51 and the same Lakland hybrid pickup as the US-made 44-51M. The 44-51 captures the rich and defined power of those early basses that revolutionized the four-string low-end world. The tone and power of a well-preserved vintage instrument with flawless Lakland fretwork and neck refinements make this another of our modern classics.
		</description>
		<price>59236</price>
		<filename>b7.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1500000000027322</id>
		<name>Stagg Deluxe Electric Double Bass</name>
		<description>
				This slender upright bass features solid maple construction and state-of-the-art electronics that are specifically designed for double bass. It has a round, warm, natural sound that accurately presents the complex tone of a quality double bass.

				It has an active under saddle pickup with Volume and Bass controls. Its output scheme is ideal for practice or performance, with a 1/4 in. main output and a 1/8" Stereo mini jack input for CD/MP3 player along with a 1/8" stereo mini jack output for headphones.

				Diecast nickel machine heads, 3/4 size with included gig bag.
		</description>
		<price>42141</price>
		<filename>b8.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1274319720198</id>
		<name>BSX Bass Allegro 5-String Acoustic-Electric Upright Bass Nutmeg</name>
		<description>
				The BSX Bass Allegro 5-String acoustic-electric upright bass is the best of both worlds. For tone, you get the depth and ring of an acoustic upright bass, with extremely flexible electronics. The multi-sensor piezo bridge system coupled with active circuit Bartolini electronics sounds extremely realistic both pizzicato and bowed. BSX Allegro Series feature a 3-band EQ, on-board preamp, and an individual volume control for each string. For looks, you get one of the coolest hybrids of classical styling and modern technology you've ever seen!
		</description>
		<price>158990</price>
		<filename>b9.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1275776905714</id>
		<name>Hofner 500/2 Club Bass Guitar Sunburst</name>
		<description>
				In 1956, Walter Hofner had an idea for an amplified semi-acoustic bass. When it was brought to life, his idea resulted in a bass with a warm, woody, double-bass-like amplified tone. Many players revere Hofner basses for their historical significance, as well as for their a smooth, sweet sound and a playing ease that simply eludes most ordinary basses.

				Because the original had become so scarce and expensive, popular demand compelled Hofner to re-create the Club Bass 500/2. The new Club Bass shares the feel, tone, and many features of the Vintage '63 but with a more traditional guitar body profile and a single cutaway.
		</description>
		<price>151470</price>
		<filename>b10.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1390232635154</id>
		<name>Hofner Vintage '62 Violin Left-Handed Electric Bass Guitar</name>
		<description>
				The Hofner 500/1 violin bass was designed by Walter Hofner and launched at the Frankfurt Music Messe in 1956. It has since gone on to become one of the most recognizable electric bass guitars in the music world in terms of both looks and sound.

				This special version was inspired by a bass made in August 1963 for Paul McCartney. It has a fully hollow body and original Hofner slim neck profile for added sustain and playability.

				Includes a Hofner Vintage strap and Hofner case.
		</description>
		<price>139731</price>
		<filename>b11.png</filename>
	</product>
	<product>
		<category>Bass</category>
		<id>1500000048386</id>
		<name>Lakland Classic 44-14 Rosewood Fretboard Electric Bass Guitar Tobacco Sunburst</name>
		<description>
				The Lakland Classic 44-14 electric bass offers American-made mastery with timeless good looks and playability. It features a 34-in. scale quarter-sawn rock maple neck with graphite reinforcement for ultimate stability. The rosewood fretboard is loaded with 22 frets and a 10 in. radius with a bone nut. Electronics are handled by a humbucker/single-coil setup of Lakland MM and Vintage J pickups with versatile controls that include a 3-band EQ, blend knob, master volume (with pull for preamp bypass) and a 3-way coil-tap toggle.
		</description>
		<price>147360</price>
		<filename>b12.png</filename>
	</product>
</products>